Paul Otomewo

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Personal Info

Address: 24 Abina street off, Randle Ave Surulere, Lagos

Phone: 09086204095

Email: Paulotomewo3@gmmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/paul-otomewo

GitHub: github.com/00Saint00

Skills

Hypertext Markup Language (HTML) - I used it to create web pages and other documents

Cascading Style Sheet (CSS)- I use this to style web page

JavaScript – used to make the web page interactive

React – I used it to create reusable UI components and edit them based on user interaction

Redux – while I'm not very good with this I use it as a state management library for JavaScript applications An experienced front-end developer with 1 year of experience, my objective is to advance my skills in HTML, JavaScript and other front-end technologies. I am to work in a challenging environment to refine my skills in responsive design, cross platform compatibility and performance optimization

Experience

2022-Present

Front End Developer The Bulb Africa

Responsibilities

- Worked with a team of developers (2 frontend developers, 2 backend developers and 2 DevOps engineers) to build a hospital management system.
- I built my Personal portfolio using React, Tailwind CSS and React icons.
- Implemented websites and landing pages from concepts through deployments

2021 - 2022

IT Technician / Service Help Desk

FedEx

Responsibilities

- Neatly arranged and labeled cables to prevent tangling and make future updates more efficient
- Maintained computer systems and acted as support for end user
- Answered user inquiries regarding computer software or hardware operations to resolve problems

Education

Mountain Top University

BSc Computer science

2016 - 2020

Mountain Top Sec School

 $West\ African\ Senior\ Secondary\ School\ cert.$

2014-2016